Scenic Hudson Collection: Records Relating to the Storm King Case, 1963-1981
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 8. Legal Papers, 1964-1974; 8; About 3.5 linear feet Boxes: 67 - 77 Folders: 798 - 996
  - Corps of Engineers Permits, Re: Storm King; 1972 (Folder 879, Box 71)
  - Scenic Hudson Petition to Reopen; March 1973 (Folder 880, Box 72)
  - Scenic Hudson Reply Brief; May 21, 1973 (Folder 881, Box 72)
  - Response to Con Ed. FPC Reply; May 22, 1973 (Folder 882, Box 72)
  - SHPC Application/FPC for Rehearing; June 28, 1973 (Folder 883, Box 72)
  - Scenic Hudson Brief; 10/19/73 (Folder 884, Box 72)
  - Scenic Hudson, et al, vs. Army Corps of Engineers and Con Edison - Injunction and Reply Brief; Oct. 1973 (Folder 885, Box 72)
  - Letter to Legislators, 12/14/73, and Replies; Re: Alternatives to Storm King (Folder 886, Box 72)
  - Scenic Hudson et al, vs. Howard Callaway, et al - U.S. District Court; 12/28/73 (Folder 887, Box 72)
  - Letter to Legislators, Re: Aqueduct Ad&Reactions (Folder 888, Box 72)
  - 12 - Congressmen Letters to Nassikas (Folder 889, Box 72)
  - 6 - State Striped Bass Letter; 1973 (Folder 890, Box 72)
  - Subcommittee Hearings; Feb 19-20, 1974: and Related Materials (Folder 891, Box 72)
  - Scenic Hudson et al. Vs. Army Corps of Engineers and Con Edison - Motion and Response; March 1974 (Folder 892, Box 72)
  - SHPC/ETC vs. (ACE) /CE 74-1311, SHPC Brief on 404 Per.; 4/22/74 (Folder 893, Box 72)
  - SHPC vs. ACE /CE 74-1311, Defendants’ Brief; 4/22/74 (Folder 894, Box 72)
  - SHPC /ETC vs. (ACE) /CE 74-1311, SHPC Reply Brief; 5/20/74 (Folder 895, Box 72)
  - SHPC vs. FPC, Pet. For Rev., set as order of FPC; 5/29/74 (Folder 896, Box 72)
  - Notes, FPC Motion for Stay of Construction& Responses; 5/74 (Folder 897, Box 72)
  - Project No. 2338 Cornwall, 73-2258-2259 - H.R. Fisherman’s Assoc. &Atomic Safety and Licensing Appeal; 1974 (Folder 898, Box 73)
  - U.S. Court of Appeals SHPC&HRFA Petition for Rehearing; 7/74 (Folder 899, Box 73)
  - U.S. Court of Appeals #74-1311 and #74-1421, re: ACE; 9/30/74 (Folder 900, Box 73)
  - Notice of Petition 11/7/74 (Folder 901, Box 73)
  - Opinion and Order, Re: Electric Rates; 11/12/74 (Folder 902, Box 73)
  - SHPC Motion for Expenses&Att. Fees; Dec. 1974 (Folder 903, Box 73)
  - SHPC Answer to Con. Ed. Petition, Re: Cornwall; 3/26/75 (Folder 904, Box 73)
  - Long Range Elec. System Plans; 1975 (Folder 905, Box 73)
  - Case No. 26538, Con. Ed. Electric Rates; 1975 (Folder 906, Box 73)
  - FPC Communications; July 1975 (Folder 907, Box 73)
  - NYS Public Service Commission: Legal Matters; 1975 (Folder 908, Box 73)
  - SHPC /Sierra Club Comments on Con Ed Cornwall Report and Recommendations for further PSC Action 6/11/76 (Folder 909, Box 73)
  - Cornwall Project 2338, 26538, 26827 - Briefs; 1976 (Folder 910, Box 73)
  - Cornwall Project 2338 - Briefs; 1/1977 (Folder 911, Box 73)
  - Project Oceana - Briefs (Folder 912, Box 73)
  - Briefs - Denying Hearing, Project #2338; April 20, 1977 (Folder 913, Box 73)
  - Scenic Hudson Briefs; 1976-77 (Folder 914, Box 73)
  - Solar Energy Legislation, Duryea; Jan. 1977 (Folder 915, Box 73)
  - Briefs; 11/21/78 (Folder 916, Box 73)
  - Crafts, Edward C. (Folder 917, Box 74)
  - Gottschalk, John S. (Folder 918, Box 74)
  - Lurkis, Alexander (Folder 919, Box 74)
  - Lurkis, Alexander (Folder 920, Box 74)
  - Mara, Lynn (Folder 921, Box 74)
  - Senator Mansfield (Folder 922, Box 74)
  - Wilbur D. Marsh (Folder 923, Box 74)
  - Margolies, Eugene - Motion for and Oral Argument of; 3/9/70 (Folder 924, Box 74)
  - Nancy Matthews (Folder 925, Box 74)
  - McNew, George L. (Folder 926, Box 74)
  - James L. Mullarkey (Folder 927, Box 74)
  - Joseph X. Mullin (Folder 928, Box 74)
  - Nassau County Fish&Game (Folder 929, Box 74)
  - National Party Boat Owners Alliance (Folder 930, Box 74)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation (Folder 931, Box 74)
  - Nature Conservancy (Folder 932, Box 74)
  - New York State Water Resources Commission: Robert A. Cook (Folder 933, Box 74)
  - Eugene H. Nickerson (Folder 934, Box 74)
  - Pearson Testimony (Folder 935, Box 74)
  - Joseph W. Penfold (Izaak Walton League) (Folder 936, Box 74)
  - Alfred Perlmutter (Folder 937, Box 75)
  - Harold A. Peterson (Folder 938, Box 75)
  - James M. Quigley (Folder 939, Box 75)
  - Mark E. Richardson (Folder 940, Box 75)
  - Ross, Charles R. - Statement; 3/9/65 (Folder 941, Box 75)
  - Val Ruge (Folder 942, Box 75)
  - Dr. Philip C. Rutledge (Folder 943, Box 75)
  - Michael Sampson (Folder 944, Box 75)
  - Alexander Saunders (Folder 945, Box 75)
  - Jean Saunders (Folder 946, Box 75)
  - Vincent J. Scully (Folder 947, Box 75)
  - Jack Shepley (FPC Staff) (Folder 948, Box 75)
  - E. Barret Shew (Folder 949, Box 75)
  - Anthony Wayne Smith (Folder 950, Box 75)
  - Joseph Solters (FPC Staff) (Folder 951, Box 75)
  - Fred C. Stein (NYC) Direct Testimony; 3/69 (Folder 952, Box 75)
  - Lyall L. Stuart (Folder 953, Box 75)
  - Robert J. Sweeney (Folder 954, Box 75)
  - John J. Tamsen (Folder 955, Box 75)
  - Teller Testimony (Folder 956, Box 75)
  - Trommershausen, William E. (Folder 957, Box 75)
  - John M. Vallance (FPC Staff) (Folder 958, Box 75)
  - R. Vandivert, HTLRC (Folder 959, Box 75)
  - Wagner, Charles H. - Testimony (Folder 960, Box 75)
  - Walburg, Charles H. (Folder 961, Box 75)
  - M.L. Waring - Cross-examination before FPC; Dec. 16, 1966 &1/4/67 (Folder 962, Box 75)
  - Waring, M.L. - Prepared Testimony (Folder 963, Box 76)
  - Herbert C. Westfall (Folder 964, Box 76)
  - James Ross Westman (Folder 965, Box 76)
  - Westport Striped Bass Club (Folder 966, Box 76)
  - Maxwell C. Wheat (Folder 967, Box 76)
  - Lee C. White (Folder 968, Box 76)
  - Samuel Wilkinson (Folder 969, Box 76)
  - John L. Wilson, President of L.I.L of Salt Water Sportsman, Inc. (Folder 970, Box 76)
  - Gerald Wilson (FPC Staff) (Folder 971, Box 76)
  - Conrad L. Wirth, Testimony; 1969 (Folder 972, Box 76)
  - James P. Wright (NYC), Testimony (Direct); 3/69 (Folder 973, Box 76)
  - Rudolph G. Wunderlich (Folder 974, Box 76)
  - Jerome Wyckoff (Folder 975, Box 76)
  - Scott Warthin Jr. (Folder 976, Box 76)
  - Duncan Exhibit #1 (Folder 977, Box 76)
  - Duncan Exhibit #2 (Folder 978, Box 76)
  - Fisk Exhibits #’s 1-5 (Folder 979, Box 76)
  - Kinnard Exhibit #1 (Folder 980, Box 76)
  - Marsh Exhibit #3 (Folder 981, Box 76)
  - Mullarkey Exhibit R - 1 (Folder 982, Box 76)
  - Neale Exhibit #1 (Folder 983, Box 76)
  - Palisades Interstate Park Commission, Land Acquisition Exhibit 2 (Folder 984, Box 76)
  - (Box 76)
  - Pearson Exhibit #1 (Folder 985, Box 76)
  - Shew Exhibit #1 (Folder 986, Box 76)
  - FPC Exhibit R Appendix A, Waring Exhibit #5 (Folder 987, Box 76)
  - Corrections to Testimony; 1966-67 (Folder 988, Box 76)
  - Excerpts of Testimony at FPC 1966 Hearings (Folder 989, Box 76)
  - Map Showing Site 1 and Site 2 (Folder 990, Box 76)
  - Legislative Bills in New York State Assembly and Related (Folder 991, Box 77)
  - Legislative Bills, House of Representatives; 1964-1974 (Folder 992, Box 77)
  - Legislative Bills, U.S. Senate (Folder 993, Box 77)
  - Legislation and Related Materials (Folder 994, Box 77)
  - Legislation and Related Materials (Folder 995, Box 77)
  - Legislation and Related Materials (Folder 996, Box 77)
- 9. Meetings, 1965-1975; 9; About 3 linear feet Boxes: 78- 81 Folders: 997 - 1110
  Series contains agenda, minutes, informational materials, and notices of board meetings, 1965-1975, arranged chronologically.
  - SHPC Meetings; 1965 (Folder 997, Box 78)
  - SHPC Meeting; 2/24/65 (Folder 998, Box 78)
  - SHPC Meetings; 1966 (Folder 999, Box 78)
  - SHPC Meetings; 1967 (Folder 1000, Box 78)
  - Agenda Feb. 16th Meeting, Scenic Hudson; 1967 (Folder 1001, Box 78)
  - Meeting March 1, 1967 (Folder 1002, Box 78)
  - Meeting, Princeton Club; 3/15/67 (Folder 1003, Box 78)
  - Scenic Hudson Development Comm. Meeting; 12:30, Thursday (Folder 1004, Box 78)
  - (Box 78)
  - SHPC Meeting; May 4, 1967 (Folder 1005, Box 78)
  - Meeting May 15, 1967; Ad Hoc Committee (Folder 1006, Box 78)
  - Meeting Ad Hoc Comm. May 22, 1967 (Folder 1007, Box 78)
  - Meeting; June 1, 1967 (Folder 1008, Box 78)
  - Meeting; June 5, 1967 (Folder 1009, Box 78)
  - Meeting; Jan. 29, 1968 (Folder 1010, Box 78)
  - SHPC Meeting; 4/10/68 (Folder 1011, Box 78)
  - SHPC Meeting; May 1, 1968 (Folder 1012, Box 78)
  - Meeting; 5/16/68 (Folder 1013, Box 78)
  - Meeting; June 20, 1968 (Folder 1014, Box 78)
  - SHPC Board Meeting; 7/24/68 (Folder 1015, Box 78)
  - Meeting; August 15, 1968 (Folder 1016, Box 78)
  - S.H. Meeting; 9/16/68 (Folder 1017, Box 78)
  - Meeting; 10/17/68 (Folder 1018, Box 78)
  - S.H. Meeting; Nov. 21, 1968 (Folder 1019, Box 78)
  - S.H. Meeting; Dec. 19, 1968 (Folder 1020, Box 78)
  - SHPC Meetings; 1965 (997, Box 78)
  - SHPC Meeting; 2/24/65 (Folder 998, Box 78)
  - SHPC Meetings; 1966 (Folder 999, Box 78)
  - SHPC Meetings; 1967 (Folder 1000, Box 78)
  - Agenda Feb. 16th Meeting, Scenic Hudson; 1967 (Folder 1001, Box 78)
  - Meeting March 1, 1967 (Folder 1002, Box 78)
  - Meeting, Princeton Club; 3/15/67 (Folder 1003, Box 78)
  - Scenic Hudson Development Comm. Meeting; 12:30, Thursday March 30, 1967 (Folder 1004, Box 78)
  - SHPC Meeting; May 4, 1967 (Folder 1005, Box 78)
  - Meeting May 15, 1967; Ad Hoc Committee (Folder 1006, Box 78)
  - Meeting Ad Hoc Comm. May 22, 1967 (Folder 1007, Box 78)
  - Meeting; June 1, 1967 (Folder 1008, Box 78)
  - Meeting; June 5, 1967 (Folder 1009, Box 78)
  - Meeting; Jan. 29, 1968 (Folder 1010, Box 78)
  - SHPC Meeting; 4/10/68 (Folder 1011, Box 78)
  - SHPC Meeting; May 1, 1968 (Folder 1012, Box 78)
  - Meeting; 5/16/68 (Folder 1013, Box 78)
  - Meeting; June 20, 1968 (Folder 1014, Box 78)
  - SHPC Board Meeting; 7/24/68 (Folder 1015, Box 78)
  - Meeting; August 15, 1968 (Folder 1016, Box 78)
  - S.H. Meeting; 9/16/68 (Folder 1017, Box 78)
  - Meeting; 10/17/68 (Folder 1018, Box 78)
  - S.H. Meeting; Nov. 21, 1968 (Folder 1019, Box 78)
  - S.H. Meeting; Dec. 19, 1968 (Folder 1020, Box 78)
  - Meeting; Jan. 16, 1969 (Folder 1021, Box 79)
  - S.H. Meeting; Feb. 20, 1969 (Folder 1022, Box 79)
  - Meeting; March 20, 1969 (Folder 1023, Box 79)
  - Meeting; April 17, 1969 (Folder 1024, Box 79)
  - Scenic Hudson Meeting; June 16, 1969 (Folder 1025, Box 79)
  - S.H. Board Meeting; June 19, 1969 (Folder 1026, Box 79)
  - S.H.P.C. Meeting; July 17 1969 (Folder 1027, Box 79)
  - Meeting; July 17, 1969 (Folder 1028, Box 79)
  - Meeting; August 14, 1969 (Folder 1029, Box 79)
  - Meeting; August 21, 1969 (Folder 1030, Box 79)
  - SHPC Meeting; 9/18/69 (Folder 1031, Box 79)
  - Meeting; Oct. 16, 1969 (Folder 1032, Box 79)
  - S.H. Meeting; Nov. 20, 1969 (Folder 1033, Box 79)
  - S.H. Meeting; Dec. 18, 1969 (Folder 1034, Box 79)
  - Financial (Scenic Hudson); 1968-69 (Folder 1035, Box 79)
  - Meeting; Jan 15, 1970 (Folder 1036, Box 79)
  - Meeting; Feb. 19, 1970 (Folder 1037, Box 79)
  - Meeting; March 19, 1970 (Folder 1038, Box 79)
  - Meeting; April 30, 1970 (Folder 1039, Box 79)
  - Meeting; May 27, 1970 (Folder 1040, Box 79)
  - Meeting; June 18, 1970 (Folder 1041, Box 79)
  - Meeting; July 16, 1970 (Folder 1042, Box 79)
  - Meeting; Sept. 17,1970 (Folder 1043, Box 79)
  - Meeting; Oct. 15, 1970 (Folder 1044, Box 79)
  - Meeting; Nov. 11, 1970 (Folder 1045, Box 79)
  - Meeting; Dec. 17, 1970 (Folder 1046, Box 79)
  - Meeting; Dec. 17, 1970 (Folder 1047, Box 79)
  - Agenda& Financial Report; Jan. 1971 (Folder 1048, Box 80)
  - Agenda& Financial Report; Feb. 1971 (Folder 1049, Box 80)
  - Agenda& Financial Report; March 1971 (Folder 1050, Box 80)
  - Agenda& Financial Report; April 1970 (Folder 1051, Box 80)
  - Minutes, Agenda& Financial Report; May 1971 (Folder 1052, Box 80)
  - Agenda, Minutes& Financial Report; June 1971 (Folder 1053, Box 80)
  - Financial Report; July 1971 (Folder 1054, Box 80)
  - Agenda& Financial Report; Aug. 1971 (Folder 1055, Box 80)
  - Minutes, Agenda& Financial Report; Sept. 1971 (Folder 1056, Box 80)
  - Agenda& Financial Report; Oct. 1971 (Folder 1057, Box 80)
  - Agenda; Nov. 1971 (Folder 1058, Box 80)
  - Agenda& Financial Report; Dec. 1971 (Folder 1059, Box 80)
  - Notice of Meetings& Misc.; 1967-71 (Folder 1060, Box 80)
  - Financial& Grants; 1971, Jan. 1972 (Folder 1061, Box 80)
  - Agenda& Financial Report; Feb. 1972 (Folder 1062, Box 80)
  - Agenda& Financial Report; March 1972 (Folder 1063, Box 80)
  - Agenda& Financial Report; April 1972 (Folder 1064, Box 80)
  - Agenda& Financial Report; May 1972 (Folder 1065, Box 80)
  - SHPC Meeting; June 1972 (Folder 1066, Box 80)
  - Agreement, 373 5th Ave.; July 1972 (Folder 1067, Box 80)
  - Agenda& Financial Report; Aug. 1972 (Folder 1068, Box 80)
  - SHPC Meeting, Agenda& Financial Report; Sept. 1972 (Folder 1069, Box 80)
  - Financial Report; Oct. 1972 (Folder 1070, Box 80)
  - Financial Report; Nov. 1972 (Folder 1071, Box 80)
  - Minutes& Financial Report; Dec. 1972 (Folder 1072, Box 80)
  - Minutes& Financial Report; Jan. 1973 (Folder 1073, Box 80)
  - Minutes, Agenda& Financial Report; Feb. 1973 (Folder 1074, Box 80)
  - Agenda& Financial Report; March 1973 (Folder 1075, Box 80)
  - Minutes, Agenda,& Financial Report; April 1973 (Folder 1076, Box 80)
  - Minutes, Agenda,& Financial Report; May 1973 (Folder 1077, Box 80)
  - Agenda; June 1973 (Folder 1078, Box 80)
  - Minutes& Agenda; July 1973 (1079, Box 81)
  - Treasurer’s Report; August 1973 (Folder 1080, Box 81)
  - Agenda& Minutes; Sept. 1973 (Folder 1081, Box 81)
  - Agenda; Oct. 1973 (Folder 1082, Box 81)
  - Agenda; Nov. 1973 (Folder 1083, Box 81)
  - Minutes& Financial Report; Dec. 1973 (Folder 1084, Box 81)
  - January 1974 (Folder 1085, Box 81)
  - Agenda& Financial Report; Feb. 1974 (Folder 1086, Box 81)
  - March 1974 (Folder 1087, Box 81)
  - Minutes, Agenda& Financial Report; April 1974 (Folder 1088, Box 81)
  - Agenda& Financial Report; May 1974 (Folder 1089, Box 81)
  - Minutes, Agenda& Financial Report; June 1974 (Folder 1090, Box 81)
  - Minutes& Financial Report; July 1974 (Folder 1091, Box 81)
  - Financial Report; Aug. 1974 (Folder 1092, Box 81)
  - September 1974 (Folder 1093, Box 81)
  - October 1974 (Folder 1094, Box 81)
  - November 1974 (Folder 1095, Box 81)
  - December 1974 (Folder 1096, Box 81)
  - Agenda& Financial Report; Jan. 1975 (Folder 1097, Box 81)
  - Minutes& Financial Report; Feb. 1975 (Folder 1098, Box 81)
  - Minutes, Agenda& Financial Report; March 1975 (Folder 1099, Box 81)
  - Minutes, Agenda& Financial Report; April 1975 (Folder 1100, Box 81)
  - Minutes, Agenda& Financial Report; May 1975 (Folder 1101, Box 81)
  - Minutes, Agenda& Financial Report; June 1975 (Folder 1102, Box 81)
  - Minutes, Agenda& Financial Report; July 1975 (Folder 1103, Box 81)
  - Financial Report; Aug. 1975 (Folder 1104, Box 81)
  - Minutes, Agenda& Financial Report; Sept 1975 (Folder 1105, Box 81)
  - Minutes& Financial Report; Oct. 1975 (Folder 1106, Box 81)
  - Agenda; Nov. 1975 (Folder 1107, Box 81)
  - Minutes, Agenda& Financial Report; Annual Meeting - Dec. 18, 1975 (Folder 1108, Box 81)
  - Scenic Hudson By-Laws& Misc. Information (Folder 1109, Box 81)
  - Important Dates in Scenic Hudson’s History (Folder 1110, Box 81)
- 10. Other Organizations and Individuals Concerned with the Storm King Case, 1965-1976; 10; about 3.5 linear feet Boxes: 82 - 93 Folders: 1111 - 1311
  Arranged alphabetically by name of organization or by surname of the individual. The organizations include the AFL-CIO, Army Corps of Engineers, Atomic Energy Commission, Audubon Society, Town of Cornwall, Harvard University, Hudson River Valley Commission, Hudson River Fishermen’s Association, National Trust for Historic Preservation, Nature Conservancy, Sierra Club, and the Wilderness Society. Individuals include C. Girard Davidson, Henry Diamond, John G. Dow, Jerome Kretchmer, John Lindsay, Roberty Moses, Eugene H. Nickerson, Richard Ottinger, Lelan F. Sillin, Jr., Lyall Stuart, and John J. Tamsen.
  - Action for the Preservation and Conservation of the North Shore, L.I. (Folder 1111, Box 82)
  - Adirondack Mountain Club (Folder 1112, Box 82)
  - Agricultural Conservation Program (Folder 1113, Box 82)
  - American Forestry Association (Folder 1114, Box 82)
  - American Nature Study Society (Folder 1115, Box 82)
  - American Scandinavian Society (Folder 1116, Box 82)
  - American Youth Hostels (Folder 1117, Box 82)
  - Appalachian Highlands Association, Inc. (AHA) (Folder 1118, Box 82)
  - NY Chapter of the Appalachian Mt. Club& NY Chapter of the Adirondack Mt. Club, Petition - March 11, 1966, and Misc. (Folder 1119, Box 82)
  - Army Corps of Engineers: Storm King Case, 1966-72 (Folder 1120, Box 82)
  - Army Corps of Engineers: Butzel Letter; Jan. 24, 1973 (Folder 1121, Box 82)
  - Army Corps of Engineers: U.S. District Court; Oct. 9, 1973 (Folder 1122, Box 82)
  - Army Corps of Engineers: Judge Lasker’s Decision; Dec. 28, 1973 (Folder 1123, Box 82)
  - Army Corps of Engineers: Reply to Butzel Letter; Feb. 4, 1974 (Folder 1124, Box 82)
  - Army Corps of Engineers: Public Notice, Re: 404 Permit (Folder 1125, Box 82)
  - Army Corps of Engineers: Letter of Objections by Butzel; March 8, 1974 (Folder 1126, Box 82)
  - Scenic Hudson et al, Vs. Army Corps of Engineers and Consolidated Edison - Court Decision; June 11, 1974 (Folder 1127, Box 82)
  - Associated Industries of New York State; 1966 (Folder 1128, Box 82)
  - Atomic Energy Commission (Folder 1129, Box 83)
  - Atomic Energy Commission /Atomic Safety and Licensing Board: Con Edison Operating License Initial Decision; Sept, 25, 1973 (Folder 1130, Box 83)
  - Atomic Energy Commission: Position of Hudson River Fisherman’s Association on Research Program Proposed by Con Edison (Folder 1131, Box 83)
  - Atomic Energy Commission: Con Edison Indian Point, Unit No. 2, Memo and Order; Jan. 29, 1974 (Folder 1132, Box 83)
  - Atomic Energy Commission: Decision on Con Edison, Indian Point No. 2; 4/4/74 (Folder 1133, Box 83)
  - Audubon Society (Folder 1134, Box 83)
  - Berkshire - Litchfield Environmental Conservancy Council, Inc. (Folder 1135, Box 83)
  - Bethlehem Rod and Gun Club, Inc. Petition; March 9, 1966 (Folder 1136, Box 83)
  - Block Rock Fish and Game Club Petition; Feb. 23, 1966 (Folder 1137, Box 83)
  - Boscobel Restoration, Inc. Petition; March 15, 1966 (Folder 1138, Box 83)
  - Bucks County Planning Commission (Folder 1139, Box 83)
  - Building and Construction Trades Dept. Petition; March 11, 1966 (Folder 1140, Box 83)
  - Catskill Aqueduct (Folder 1141, Box 83)
  - Central Hudson Gas& Electric Corporation (Folder 1142, Box 84)
  - Central Park (Folder 1143, Box 84)
  - Chester County Conservation Committee (Folder 1144, Box 84)
  - Citizens Committee for the Hudson Valley (Folder 1145, Box 84)
  - Citizens Committee for the Hudson Valley: Bulletins (Folder 1146, Box 84)
  - Citizens Committee on Natural Resources; 1966-70 (Folder 1147, Box 84)
  - Citizens Information Committee (Folder 1148, Box 84)
  - Citizens Organizing Committee (Folder 1149, Box 84)
  - Citizens Standing Committees (Folder 1150, Box 84)
  - Commerce and Industry Association of New York, Inc. - Petition; March 2, 1966 (Folder 1151, Box 84)
  - Congress of Puerto Rican Municipalities Petition; Feb. 23, 1965 (Folder 1152, Box 84)
  - Connecticut Valley Action Committee (Folder 1153, Box 84)
  - Conservation Center (Folder 1154, Box 84)
  - Conservation Forum (Folder 1155, Box 84)
  - Conservation League (Folder 1156, Box 84)
  - Conservation Organizations (Folder 1157, Box 84)
  - Conservation Planners (Folder 1158, Box 84)
  - Constitution Island Association; 1966-70 (Folder 1159, Box 84)
  - Cornwall -on- Hudson (Folder 1160, Box 84)
  - Cornwall Sloop Group (Folder 1161, Box 84)
  - Cornwall, Town of - Petitions; 1966, 1968 (Folder 1162, Box 84)
  - Cornwall Central School District Board of Education - Petition; 2/23/66 (Folder 1163, Box 84)
  - Cornwall Taxpayers Association Petition; Feb. 23, 1966 (Folder 1164, Box 84)
  - Cornwall Taxpayers Water Protection Association - Clippings (Folder 1165, Box 84)
  - Cornwall vs. EPA of New York City, Appellate’s Brief; Mar. 15, 1974 (Folder 1166, Box 84)
  - Cortlandt Conservation Association; 1964, 1966 (Folder 1167, Box 85)
  - Council of Brooklyn Organizations Petitions; 1965-66 (Folder 1168, Box 85)
  - Croton Aqueduct (Folder 1169, Box 85)
  - Defenders of Wildlife (Folder 1170, Box 85)
  - Ecological Research Bill (Folder 1171, Box 85)
  - Economic Development Council of New York City - Petitions; 1966 (Folder 1172, Box 85)
  - Empire State Chamber of Commerce Petition; Feb. 21, 1966 (Folder 1173, Box 85)
  - Federation of New York State Bird Clubs (Folder 1174, Box 85)
  - Freeport, NY, Incorporated Village of Petitions; 1965-66 (Folder 1175, Box 85)
  - Friends of Animals (Folder 1176, Box 85)
  - Friends of the Hudson (Larry Bogart) (Folder 1177, Box 85)
  - Fuels Research Council, Inc. National Coal Association, United Mine Workers of America - Joint Petition; July 21, 1966 (Folder 1178, Box 85)
  - Garden Club of America (Folder 1179, Box 85)
  - Garrison Fish and Game Club - Petition; March 14, 1966 (Folder 1180, Box 85)
  - Green Mountain Club (Bill Bartlett) (Folder 1181, Box 85)
  - Greenbelt Emergency Conference on Richmond Expressway (Folder 1182, Box 85)
  - Harvard Commission Report, Reaction to; Jan. 18, 1973 (Folder 1183, Box 85)
  - Harvard University - Earth Day; 1970 (Folder 1184, Box 85)
  - Hempstead Town Land Resources Council; 1965, 1968 (Folder 1185, Box 85)
  - Highlands, Town of - Petition; Feb. 23, 1966 (Folder 1186, Box 85)
  - Highlands, Town of - Fish and Game Club, Inc. Petition; March 10, 1966 (Folder 1187, Box 85)
  - Hilltop Village Crops; 1965-66 (Folder 1188, Box 85)
  - Hudson Highland State Park - Clippings (Folder 1189, Box 86)
  - Hudson River Conservation Society (Folder 1190, Box 86)
  - Hudson River Environmental Society, Inc. (Folder 1191, Box 86)
  - Hudson River Fisherman’s Association - Brief on Exceptions; Oct. 7, 1968 (Folder 1192, Box 86)
  - Hudson River Fisherman’s Association: Release and Petition; Feb 2, 1973 (Folder 1193, Box 86)
  - Hudson River Fisherman’s Association: Amicus Curiae Brief; 2/8/73 (Folder 1194, Box 86)
  - Hudson River Fisherman’s Association and Scenic Hudson vs. FPC and Con Edison; Dec. 5, 1973 (Folder 1195, Box 86)
  - Hudson River Fisherman’s Association and Scenic Hudson vs. FPC and Con Edison; Jan 16, 1974 (Folder 1196, Box 86)
  - Hudson River Fisherman’s Association - Washington Hearings Legal Documents; Oct. - Dec. 1974 (Folder 1197, Box 86)
  - Hudson River Fisherman’s Association: Washington Hearings, Legal Documents, Jan. 1975 (Folder 1198, Box 86)
  - Hudson River Fisherman’s Association: Washington Hearings, Legal Documents; Feb. 1975 - Jan. 1976 (Folder 1199, Box 86)
  - Hudson River Fisherman’s Association: Washington Hearings, Notes (Folder 1200, Box 86)
  - Hudson River Fisherman’s Association and Scenic Hudson vs. FPC and con Edison - Appeal Court Decision; May 8, 1974 (Folder 1201, Box 86)
  - Hudson River Fisherman’s Association and Scenic Hudson vs. FPC and Con Edison - Petition for Rehearing (Con Ed); May 22, 1974 (Folder 1202, Box 87)
  - Hudson River Fisherman’s Association and Scenic Hudson vs. FPC and Con Edison - Petition for Rehearing/Stay; May 22, 1974 (Folder 1203, Box 87)
  - Hudson River Fisherman’s Association and Scenic Hudson vs. FPC and Con Edison - Petitions for Rehearing; July 1, 1974 (Folder 1204, Box 87)
  - Hudson River Fisherman’s Association, et al. Vs. FPC and Con Edison - Brief in Opposition to Dissolve Deadline; May 9, 1975 (Folder 1205, Box 87)
  - Hudson River - General (Folder 1206, Box 87)
  - Hudson River Valley Association (Folder 1207, Box 87)
  - Hudson River Valley Commission; 1965 (Folder 1208, Box 87)
  - Hudson River Valley Commission; 1966-67 (Folder 1209, Box 87)